https://www.thelawbookstore.com/legal_books/pc/Privacy-Policy-d3.htm

The cart is empty.
{{shoppingcart.totalQuantityDisplay}}
Total:
View Cart {{shoppingcart.totalQuantityDisplay}}
Item(s)
Stay Connected:
(714)491-2665
The cart is empty.
{{shoppingcart.totalQuantityDisplay}}
Total:
View Cart {{shoppingcart.totalQuantityDisplay}}
Item(s)
Professional Books
AILA Immigration Title...
AILA Immigration Title...
Professional Books
BNA Bureau of National...
Student Books
"Used" Texts and Study...
Rigos Review Books
Aspen Publishing Caseb...
Aspen Roadmap Outlines
Bar None Essay Writer
Bar Secrets
Barcharts
Carolina Academic Pres...
Casenote Legal Briefs
Casenote Legal Briefs
Casenote Legal Briefs
CEB
Concepts and Insights...
Concepts and Insights...
Emanuel Crunch Time Se...
Emanuel Law Outlines
Employment Guides
Essay Exam Writing
Examples & Explana...
EZ Rules
Fleming's Fundamentals...
Fleming's Fundamentals...
Fleming's Fundamentals...
Fleming's Fundamentals...
Friedman's Practice Se...
Gilbert Law School Sum...
High Court Case Summar...
Law Dictionaries
Law in a Flash Flashca...
Law School Prep
Legal Writing Books
Lexis Student Guides
Matthew Bender Questio...
Matthew Bender Student...
Student Textbooks
Study Partner Exam Wri...
Study Partner Foldeez...
Study Partner Issue Sp...
Sum And Substance Audi...
Sum And Substance Quic...
Taines Issue Spotting
Understanding Series
West Publishing Black...
West Publishing Casebo...
West Publishing Exam P...
West Publishing hornbo...
West Publishing Hornbo...
West Publishing HornBo...
West Publishing Nutshe...
West Publishing Nutshe...
West Publishing Studen...
Gilbert Law School Leg...
Contact Us
Visit us at Facebook:
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app? When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your None or other details to help you with your experience. When do we collect information? We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, fill out a form or enter information on our site. How do we use your information? We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. To improve our website in order to better serve you. To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. To quickly process your transactions. To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
How do we protect visitor information? Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers. Do we use 'cookies'? We do not use cookies for tracking purposes You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders. Third Party Disclosure We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. Third party links We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website. Google Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future. California Online Privacy Protection Act CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: https://consumercal.org/about-cfc/cfc-education-foundation/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa-3/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
• On our Privacy Policy Page Users are able to change their personal information:
• By emailing us
• By calling us
• By logging in to their account How does our site handle do not track signals? We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking? It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking. COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act) When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children under 13. Fair Information Practices The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users via email within 7 business days We will notify the users via in site notification within 7 business days
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
About Us
We are a full service Legal Bookstore offering a wide variety of Law Student Texts and Study Aids New and Used. We also carry a full line of Professional California Attorney Guides. Check on our ever-changing inventory! 714-491-2665
Company
Our Team
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Address
The Law Bookstore
1775 W. La Palma Ave.
Anaheim, CA 92801
Copyright ©2008-2020 Law Book Store.
All Rights Reserved.
https://www.thelawbookstore.com
×
Global Message
Quick View
